Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual, step inside the flow
The circus of shadows, its psyches show
Terrible trolls in the dark take their stand
But angels are dancing, torchlight and haze
Stranger
Are
Thanks for watching!
And slay the dead
Dance like you're a wakens, don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
goes fall
I've been missing in my sleep
Like it's his patrol, oh page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Musician to a mastermind plot and world peace and full view
I tell him my secrets. He keeps them all safe. He's the Watson to my Sherlock my quantum soulmate
He's never too busy. Never too mean doesn't judge me when my room's not clean. Sometimes I wonder if you
Data streams down this lover's road
From here...
Don't you dare tell me it's not real
And the chat still bleeds.
There's a light through the chaos, a vibe so true.
That's all because of every single one of you.